Guide to the Sloan Program in Health Services Administration records, 1983-2012.
Sloan Program in Health Services Administration records, 1983-2010.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Sloan Program in Health Services Administration records, 1983-2012.
23-26-3273
New York State College of Human Ecology. Sloan Program in Health Services Administration.
5.4 cubic ft.
Minutes, correspondence, photographs, and alumni directories.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes minutes of meetings, correspondence, photographs, and alumni directories concerning the Sloan Program in Health Services Administration.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
The Sloan Program was founded in 1955 as part of the Cornell Graduate School of Business and Public Administration. In 1984 it transfered to the Dept. of Human Service Studies, now called Policy Analysis and Management, in the New York State College of Human Ecology. In October of 1987 the faculty of the College of Human Ecology voted unanimously to make the Sloan Program a permanent part of the College.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes minutes of meetings, correspondence, photographs, and alumni directories concerning the Sloan Program in Health Services Administration.
SUBJECTS
Names:
New York State College of Human Ecology. Sloan Program in Health Services Administration.; Cornell University. Graduate School of Business and Public Administration.; New York State College of Human Ecology. Dept. of Policy Analysis and Management.; New York State College of Human Ecology. Dept. of Human Service Studies.
Subjects:
Public health--New York (State)--Tompkins County.; Public health administration--Handbooks, Manuals, etc.
Form and Genre Terms:
Photographs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Additional material and digital versions can be found online here: http://ecommons.cornell.edu/handle/1813/11741
SERIES LIST
Series I. Reports/Proposals/Reviews
Series II. Board Meetings/Class Material
Series III. Correspondence
Series IV. Programs and internships
Series V. Associations and Committees
Series VI. Grants
Series VII. Publications/Publicity
Series VIII. Scholarships and Awards
Series IX. Resumes and Class Lists
Series X. Resumes and Class Lists
Series XI. Conferences
Series XII. Photographs
Series XIII. Miscellaneous
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Reports/Proposals/Reviews
  - Master of Professional Studies Program in Health Services Administration at Cornell, March 1984 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Proposal for MHA Program in Health Administration, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Visitor's Report on the Sloan Program, February 1987 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - 30th Anniversary of the Sloan Program in Health Administration, October 1989 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Proposal for MHA Program in Health Administration, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Progress Report, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Health Program Progress Report, February 1987 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Sloan Program in Health Services Administration, November 1988 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Letter of Intent- MPS to MHA Conversion, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Accreditation Report (1), 1989 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Accreditation Report (2), 1989 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Progress Reports- First Year, 1990 & March 1991 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Supplement to Proposal to Offer the MHA at the New York State College of Human Ecology in the Department of Human Service Studies Sloan Program in Health Services Administration, October 1991 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Site Visit Committee Report, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Progress Report-August, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Progress Report to ACEHSA, April 1992 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - ACEHSA Self-Study for Grad Programs in Health Services Administration (1), 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - ACEHSA Self-Study for Grad Programs in Health Services Administration (2), 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - ACEHSA- Volume II- Course Syllabi (3), 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - ACEHSA- Volume II- Course Syllabi (4), 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - ACEHSA- Volume II (5), 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Accreditation Report, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 5 Year Progress Report, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 3rd Year Progress Report, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Future of the Sloan Program-Comments by Yale, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - ACEHSA Self-Study, Fall 1998 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Self Study & Strategic Plan- Draft & Program Material, September 1999 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Strategic Plan- PAM (draft), March 2000 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Strategic Plan-PAM (current), March 2001 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - External Review- PAM, August 2001 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - External Review- PAM, November 2001 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - ACEHSA- Self Study-Site Visit Accreditation, May 2001 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - ACEHSA- Self Study-Guide and Report, May 2001 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - ACEHSA- Self Study-Site Visit Accreditation, May 2001 (Box 2, Folder 34-35)
  - ACEHSA-Self Study-Faculty Vitae, May 2001 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - ACEHSA-Site Visit Team Report, May-June 2001 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - External Review- PAM, January 2002 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - External Review- Revision- PAM, April 2002 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - "Recognizing Sloan as a Partner in Health Administration"-Consulting Report, April 2002 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - ACEHSA- Progress Report, November 2002 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - ACEHSA Correspondence, 1999-2002 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Faculty Advising Notes- by Don Kenkel, August 2002 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - "Operations Management, Information Technology & the Future of Health Care"- by Liam O'Neill & Samuel Levey (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Criteria for Accreditation, September 2003 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - ACHESA-Self-Study-Site Visit Accreditation, October 2003-2004 (Box 10, Folder 2-7)
  - Curriculum, 2002-2003 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - PAM-Departmemt Annual Report, 2003-2004 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - ACEHSA-Site Visit Team Report, November 2004 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - ACEHSA-Self-Study Guide for Graduate Programs in Health Services Administration, Fall 2004 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - ACEHSA-Site Visit Team Report, May 2005 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Commission on Accreditation of Healthcare Management Education (CAHME)-Sloan Program in Health Administration- First Year Progress Report, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - (CAHME)Sloan Program in Health Administration- 2nd Year Progress Report, January 2007 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - (CAHME)Review of Sloan Program, Spring 2011 (Box 10, Folder 19-20)
- Series II. Board Meetings/Class Material
  - Program Information, 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Executive Board Meeting, 1990-1993 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Reunion- Fall, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Sloan Annual Fund, 1992-1994 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Progress Report-February, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Fall Board Meeting, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Intercession and Membership, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - By-laws, 1994 and earlier (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Winter Board Meeting, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Spring Board Meeting, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Sloan Annual Fund, 1994-1997 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Intercession Trip, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Winter Board Meeting, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Spring Board Meeting, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Fall Board Meeting, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Fall Board Meeting, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Directory, Bylaws, Meeting Minutes, 1996-2001 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Nominating Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Curriculum, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Finance Committee, 1995-1997 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Fall Board Meeting, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Winter Board Meeting, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Spring Board Meeting, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Special Board Meeting, June 1996 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Fundraising, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Reunion, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Winter Board Meeting, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Spring Board Meeting, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Fall Board Meeting, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - By-laws, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Board Meetings, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Executive Board Members, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Board Meetings, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Board Meetings, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Executive Board-Alumni Association Meetings, 2001-2004 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Material given out at Alumni Board Meetings, 2003-2004 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - PAM-Sloan Committee Meetings, 2003-2004 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Student Association Meetings, 2003-2004 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Sloan Faculty Meetings, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Board Meetings, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Board Meetings, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Board Meeting, January 2007 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Board Meeting, May 2007 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Board Meeting, October 2007 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Board Meetings, January and May 2008 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Board Meeting, September 2008 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Board Meeting, January 2009 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Board Meeting, May 2009 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Board Meeting, October 2009 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Board Meetings, January, May, October 2010 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Board Meetings, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Series III. Correspondence
  - Correspondence, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Letters of Intent and Proposals, 1984-1987 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Program Information, 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Alumni Correspondence, Accreditation, 1983-1985 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Concerning the transfer to Human Ecology, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Health Course Information, 1980s (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Program History- Correspondence, Memos, 1982-1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Program History- Correspondence, Memos, 1998-2001 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - ACEHSA Reaccreditation- (1990-91) Includes: Correspondence, Grad Course offerings (1984-1993); Class Lists (1984-1993), 1984-1993 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Early Program Correspondence- MOU, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence- concerning MHA, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence- Degree Approval & Conversion, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence- Master of Professional Studies (MPS) for 5 year students- includes reports, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence- Concerns about the Sloan Program, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence- Accreditation of 5 year Program- CAHME, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence- 5 year BS/MPS, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence- re: students, mentors, executive board, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Series IV. Programs & Internships
  - Health Executive Development Program- Friday, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Health Executive Development Program- Wednesday & Thursday- Talks, Articles, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Health Executive Development Program- Tuesday- Talks, Articles, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Health Executive Development Program- Speakers bios, program, general information, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Health Executive Development Program- Monday- Talks, Articles, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Health Executives Development Program- Flyers, 1994-1997 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Mentor Program, 1990's (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Physician Administrator Study Tour, September 1996 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Intercession Field Trip- Cornell Medical Center, January 1998 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Internships- Guidelines, timetables & residency data, 1990-2003 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Field Trips/Intercession Program, 1993-2002 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Colloquia Series: 1994-Fall 1997 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Residency Forms, 1997-2000 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Colloquia Series: Spring 1998 - Spring 2005 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Performance Management Immersion Program, February 2000 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Orientation, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Orientation, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Orientation, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Exit Interviews, 2004 and 2005 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Calendar of Events, 2006-2007 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Colloquium Series Flyers, 2006-2007 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - University of Nottingham Study Tour: "Learning from America", October 1995 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - University of Nottingham - U.S. Study Tour (1), 1998 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - University of Nottingham - U.S. Study Tour (2), 1998 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - University of Nottingham - U.S. Study Tour (1), 1997 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - University of Nottingham - U.S. Study Tour (2), 1997 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Health Executive Development Program-Courses Approved, 1988-1994 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - University of Nottingham-Physician Administrator Study Tour, September 12-13, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 76)
- Series V. Associations & Committees
  - Sloan Student Association- Finances, Phoneathon, Correspondence, Artwork, Fundraising, Rochester Trip, 1986-1992 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Sloan Student Association, 1988-1995 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Sloan Student Association Meeting Minutes, 1996-February 1999 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Certificates-ACHA-Student Chapter, 1985-2001 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Executive Board Minutes, 1999-2002 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes, August 1999-Deccember 8, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes, August 1995-April 27, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1986-July 1994 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Curriculum Planning Committee, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Series VI. Grants
  - Grants, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Grants, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Grants, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Grants, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Grants, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Grants, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Grants, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Grants, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Grants, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Grants, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Grants, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Grants, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Grants, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Grants, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Traineeships & Special Projects- Health Administration, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Traineeship & Special Projects- Health Administration, 1996-1998 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Traineeship & Special Projects- Health Administration, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Traineeships & Speical Projects- Health Administration Progress Reports, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Traineeships & Special Projects- Health Administration, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Traineeship & Special Projects- Health Administration, 1999-2002 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Traineeships & Special Projects- Health Administration, 2000-2002 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Traineeship & Special Projects- Health Administration, 2000-2003 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Traineeship & Special Projects- Health Administration, 2000-2003 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Health Administration Special Project Grant, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Series VII. Publications/Publicity
  - Alumni Directory, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Alumni Directory, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Alumni Directory, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Yearbook- "The Rubicon", 1993 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Alumni Directory, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Alumni Directory, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Alumni Directory, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Alumni Directory, 2003, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Student Handbook, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Student Handbook, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Student Handbook, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Student Handbook, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Student Handbook, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Student Handbook, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Web site, pre September 1999 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Flyer (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Policies & Procedures- PAM, September 2000 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1984-1995 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Program Summary, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Forms used by Sloan, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Brochures (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Newsletter - "Sloan Update", 1992-2005 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Newsletter- "Sloan Update", 2006-2008 (Box 1, Folder 3A)
  - Link Magazine-50th Anniversary of Sloan Program, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - "Strengthening the Future", 1998 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Admissions Material (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Advising Handbook, 2007-2008 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Series VIII. Scholarships and Awards
  - Placement- Historical Data, 1989-1999 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Financial Aid Summaries, 1984-1994 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Proposal- "Rationalizing the Decision Making Process", 1996 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Scholarships & Fellowships- Historical Data, 1993-2000 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Scholarship Recipients, 1997-2001 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Scholarships & Awards, 1997-2001 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Abbot Fellowship- AUPHA, 1978-2003 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Arkell Hall Foundation, 1997-1999 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Blue Cross/Blue Shield Case Study Competition, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Dent McGraw Scholarship, 1979-1992 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - FAH Scholarship (1985), Fitzpatrick Memorial Scholarship (1987), Laventhol & Horwath Grant (1990), 1985-1990 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Park Foundation, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Wagner Dinner-includes photos-, 1987-2000 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Wagner Dinner-invitation, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 13A)
  - Wagner Weekend-Invitations, Programs, 2005-2012 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Series IX. Resumes & Class Lists
  - Resumes of Class, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Resumes of Class, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Class Lists, 1984-2005 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Resumes of Classes, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 16A)
  - Resumes of Class, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Resumes of Class, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Resumes of Class, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Resumes of Class(some missing), 1997 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Resumes of Class (some missing), 1998 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Resumes of Class, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Resumes of Class, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Resumes of Class, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Resumes of Class, 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Resumes of Class, 2003-2004 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Resumes of Class, 2004-2005 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Resumes of Class, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 25A)
  - Resumes of Class, 2008-2009 (Box 4, Folder 25B)
  - Resumes of Class, 2010-2011 (Box 4, Folder 25C)
  - Resumes of Class, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Series X. Courses
  - Review of Core Curriculum, Spring 2004 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Course Offerings and Faculty Advisor Lists, 2004-2006 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Required Courses, 1994-1997, 2001-2003 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Course Waiver Petition Policy, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - HSS 611 (026 Spring 1996): "Health Status Measurement & Outcomes Evaluation" (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - HSS 612 (26 Spring 1994 & 1995): "Epidemiology, Clinical Medicine & Management Interface Issue" (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - HSS 612 (32 Spring 1993): "Quality in Health Care Organizations", HSS 628- Spring 1993- "Medical Service Issues in Health Care Administration" (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - HSS 612 (36 Fall 1993): "Managing Health & Human Service Organizations" (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - HSS 612 (45 Fall 1993): "Negotiations", HSS 613 (Fall 1993): Seminar on Mental Health & Related Services" (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - HSS 612 (63 Spring 1994): "Health Care Finance II: Payment Systems" (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - HSS 625 (Fall 1994 & 1995): "Health Care Services: consumer & Ethnical Perspectives"; HSS 634- Fall 1994- "Health Care Organizations" (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - HSS 627 (Spring 1994-1996): "Leagal Aspects of Health Services Delivery" (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - HSS 692 (Spring 1993): "Strategic Planning & Marketing in Health Care"; HSS 631 (Ps 1993 & 1995-1996): "Managed Health Delivery Systems: Primary Ambulatory Care" (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - HSS 634 (Fall 1993 & 1995-1996): "Health Care Organizations"; HSS 600-02 (Spring 1993): "Health Care Payment System" (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - HSS 636 (Spring 1993): "The Financial Management of Health & Human Service Organizations" (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - HSS 642 (Spring 1995): "Health Care Finance II: Payment Systems"; HSS 641 (Spring 1995 & 1996): "Health Care Financial Mangement I" (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - HSS 640 (Fall 1996): "Economics of Health & Medical Care" (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - HSS 648 (Fall 1994-1996); HSS 649 (Spring 1994& 97) (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - HSS 672 (Spring 1993 & 1994): "Information Resources Management for Health & Human Services Organizations" (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - HSS 685 (Fall 1995): "Health & Welfare Policy Foundations" (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - HSS 685 (Fall 1996): "Health & Welfare Policy Foundations" (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - HSS 688 (Spring 1994 & 1996): "Long Term Care & th Aged: Alternative Health & Social Service Delivery Systems" (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - HSS 690 (Fall 1994 & Fall 1993): "Measurement for Program Evaluations & Research" (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - PAM- Selected Course Descriptions, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - PAM 457 (Spring 2003): " Innovation & Entrepreneurship in the Health Care Industry"; PAM 547 (Spring 2004): "Microeconomics for Management & Policy" (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - PAM 552 (Fall 2003): "Health Care Services: Consumer & Ethical Perspectives"; PAM 337 (Fall 2003): "Health Care Organizatinos" (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - PAM 559 (2004): "Epidemiology, Clinical Medicine & Management Interface Issues"; PAM 562 (2004): "Health Care Financial Management I" (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - PAM 564 (Spring 2004): "Information Resource Management" (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - PAM 566- "H.C. Strategic Management" (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - PAM 565 (2003): "Managing Health & Human Service Organizations I"; PAM 569 (Fa 2003): "Regression Analysis & Managerial Forecasting" (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - PAM 566 (Fa 2003): "Strategic Management & Organizational Design of Health Care Systems" (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - PAM 570 (2003): "Health Care Accounting"; PAM 571 (2003): "Organizational Development/ H. R. Management" (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - PAM 573 (2004): "Seminar on Managed Care Policy & Management Issues"; PAM 579 (2004): "Financial Freud, Abuse & Compliance in Health Care" (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - PAM 632 (Fa 2003): "The Will of the People & the Power of the Gov't."; PAM 654: "Leagal Aspects of Health Care Administration"; PAM 656 (Sp 2001): "Managed Care" (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - PAM 658 (July 2000): "The Capstone Project" (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - PAM 760: "Challenges & Trends in the Health Care Industry" (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - CEH 307 (Fall 1996)-"Introduction to Econometrics" (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - HSS 631 (Spring 1997)-"Managed Health Delivery Systems: Primary-Ambulatory Care" (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - HSS 634 (Fall 1996)-"Health Services Organization & Financing" (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - HSS 637 (Spring 1997)-"Epidemology, Clinical Medicine & Management Interface Issues" (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - HSS 641 (Spring 1996)(Spring 1997)-"Health Care Financial Management" (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - HSS 642 (Spring 1997)-"Health Care Finance II: Payment Systems, Risk and Insurance" (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - HSS 649 (Spring 1997)-"Managing Health & Human Service Organizations" (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - HSS 688 (Spring 1997)-"Long Term Care & the Aged: Alternative Health and Social Service Delivery Systems" (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - HSS 699 (Spring 1997)-"Complementary Alternative Medicine" (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Student Projects
    - HSS Course, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - HSS Course-400, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - HSS Course-600, 1990s (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - HSS Course-631, 1990,1996 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - HSS Course-632, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - HSS Course-634, 1990s (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - HSS Course-636, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - HSS Course-636-Health Care Finance Projects, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - HSS Course-636-Health Care Finance Projects, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - HSS Course-636, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - HSS Course-688, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Grant and Case Studies, 1995-1999 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Case Studies, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Problem Solving Projects, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Problem Solving Projects, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 15-16)
    - Problem Solving Projects, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 17-19)